Metal Cardbot Commentary!
Metal Cardbot, Setup!
Hey, guys! I'm Jun.
Now that you're all here,
let's watch an episode of Metal Cardbot together!
It's "Metal Cardbot Commentary" time!
Blue Cop, setup!
My name is Blue Cop!
It's nice to meet so many new friends, isn't it?
Just like it was great meeting you, Blue Cop!
How about today we watch the story
of how Blue Cop and I first met?
Shall we get started?
A... robot?
This ends now, Mega Trucker!
You're coming with me.
Do you really think anyone would just play along nicely when asked something like that?!
Haha! Blue Cop!
Did you really fall over that hard just by being hit with a tire?
Ah... I let my guard down for only a moment, Jun.
Blue cop is~ So clumsy~
He tripped and~ fell over a tire!~
Ngh. Jun!
I... I'm not that weak!
There's a human here!
Tch. This isn't over!
Stop right there!
What have you done to my bike!!
And where did my helmet go?
This doesn't show us anything...
Yeah, didn't even get the license plate.
It would be nice to know the license plate for the police car-
And what would you do with that? Would you go to the police station and ask,
"Is there a car here that transforms into a robot?"
Hey, Blue Cop!
Where were you hiding before you met me?
Well, naturally...
I was living in hiding at the police station.
Were you really hiding among the police cars?
I picked it up after all of that happened.
Did the robots leave it behind?
I think so.
This looks like something you can buy anywhere these days.
Stop messing around...
Agh, I'm not! I really can't lift it! It's like it's glued to the table!
Let me try.
I can't move it at all, not even an inch!
Don't be ridiculous. See?
- Agh!
- What's going on here?!
That's what I should be asking you guys...
Back off!
J-Jun?
So you want to play the hero?
How's the robot hunt going?
I'll find it soon!
You sound confident!
I stepped in poop.
Rapid fire poop kick!!
Get away, get away!
Vance! How dare you! Aah!
Jun!
You... you stepped in poop?
You shouldn't do that to your friends with shoes you stepped in poop with!
N-no way!
I didn't actually step in poop!
It's okay, Jun.
You don't have to hide it from me.
Besides, something still smells...
No! I didn't step in poop-!
Uh... Wait a second.
You can smell?
Not good!
Nice try!
Nowhere to run now!
Hang on! Let's not resort to violence, you guys!
I said, stop it!
What's going on?
What are you trying to pull now?
Change!
Is that... the robot?
Blue Cop!
I was really surprised when you grabbed me out of nowhere like that!
I'm sorry, Jun.
In my haste, I wasn't being careful.
It was really...
So much fun! Let's do it again sometime!
You mean... you're not angry, Jun?
Angry?
I felt like I was flying!
Ha... haha!
Then let's go do it again!
My BMX that your friend crushed! You'll need to compensate me for that!
What?!
So what do you think, guys?
This is how the story of Blue Cop and I met!
Let's see each other again next time,
for the next episode of "Metal Cardbot Commentary"!